Nothing is greater.
>> Nothing is greater.
>> Nothing is sweeter.
Nothing is more important than living
our life for God.
>> Sometimes we get weary.
>> Sometimes we get all stressed out.
But nothing is more important.
>> Welcome to the Israel of God Dallas.
All
right.
Good afternoon. I'm brother Troy. Uh
today Marie will be brother Anderson
once again. Uh happy Sabbath.
>> Happy Sabbath
>> for all those that are in the house and
those that are watching us online. As
always, we like to start our our class
off with the reading of the law. So, if
we would if we all could turn to Exodus
the 20th chapter. This is where we'll
start today's lesson. Exodus the 20th
chapter.
Exodus the 20th chapter.
Everybody should already be there,
brother. You can go ahead and start to
read.
>> All right. And God spake all these words
and say,
>> what did God say?
>> I am the Lord thy God, which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt,
out of the house of bondage. Thou shalt
have no other gods before me. Thou shalt
not make unto thee any graven image, or
any likeness of anything that is in the
heaven above, or that is in the earth
beneath, or that is in the water under
the earth. Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them, nor serve them. For I,
the Lord thy God, am a jealous God,
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children, unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me,
and showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain. For the Lord will not
hold him guiltless that taketh his name
in vain. Remember the Sabbath day, to
keep it holy. Six days shalt thou labor
and do all thy work. But the seventh day
is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In
it thou shalt not do any work. Thou nor
thy son, nor thy daughter, thy man's
servant, nor thy maid servant, nor thy
cattle, for thy stranger that is in
within that is within thy gates. For in
six days the Lord made heaven and earth,
the sea, and all that in them is, and
rested the seventh day. Wherefore the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day, and
hallowed it. Honor thy father and thy
mother, that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee. Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt
not commit adultery. Thou shalt not
steal. Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbor. Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbor's house. Thou shalt
not covet thy neighbor's wife, nor his
man's servant, nor his maid servant, nor
his ox, nor his ass, nor anything that
is thy neighbors,
>> nor anything that is thy neighbor. And
all the people said, "All that the Lord
say, we will do and be obedient." Let's
go to Ecclesiastes the 12th chapter.
Once we get there, brethren, you can
pick it up at verse 13 and proceed to
read.
Let us hear the conclusion of the whole
matter. What's the conclusion of the
whole matter, brother?
>> Fear God and keep his commandments. For
this is the whole duty of man.
>> Uh-huh.
>> For God shall bring every work into
judgment with every secret thing,
whether it be good or whether it be
evil. Man, look at here. Let's go to
Revelation the 22nd chapter,
last book, last chapter,
right? and we're going to see if there
will still be emphasis placed on keeping
of God's holy commandments.
Picking up at verse 14 and you can go
ahead and start to read. Blessed are
they that do his commandments.
>> Not blessed.
>> Blessed are they that do his
commandments.
>> Just do them if you want to.
>> Blessed are they that do his
commandments.
>> Go ahead, brother. that they may have
right to the tree of life,
>> and may enter in through the gates into
the city. For without are dogs, and
sorcerers, and whoreongers, and
murderers, and idoltors, and whosoever
loveth and maketh a lie.
>> That's right. And that those gates into
that into that city is none other than
New Jerusalem, which I pray that we all
make it.
>> Amen.
>> Right. This is why we come here. This is
not just some s uh uh weekly routine
that we get in the habit of doing. The
Lord commands us in his commandments to
not just keep a convocation but a holy
convocation before him. So once again I
want to reintroduce myself for those
that may be just joining on in. I want
to say um I'm brother Troy. Today my
reader will be brother Anderson. And um
as always, I like to stop and just thank
God for allowing me once again to stand
in this position right here, right? And
speak over his people, right? As uh I
prepared this lesson, as he's prepared
me, I pray and uh that he endows me with
his Holy Spirit today and that I'm able
to do his word justice. Once again, I
thank him. With that said,
um, we'll dive right in.
In Matthew, in the Lord's Prayer, the
Matthew the 6th chapter.
In the Lord's Prayer, the scripture tell
us, "Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven."
See, as believers, we are called to be
what? kingdom- minded.
Think about that for a moment.
You know, we live in a world where
everyone is loyal to something, right?
People pledge align uh you know, their
alliance to political parties, to their
careers, to social causes, even sports
teams. I fall gratitude,
right? Every day we're influenced by
ideas
and systems that are constantly
uh competing for our attention.
Right? So if we look at if some of them
if we look at our lives today,
would they know
which kingdom that you belong to?
Somebody was to look at your life today.
Would they know just by your actions and
your deeds which kingdom you belong to?
Why would you ask that question, brother
Troy? Glad you asked because the
scripture tell us that there's a God of
this world.
>> That's right.
>> Right. Second Corinthians uh the 4th
chapter tell us if the gospel be hid, it
is hid to them that are what?
>> Lost.
>> That are lost. In whom the God of what?
of this world has blinded them.
>> Blinded them.
>> Right?
>> See the challenge for many people is
they know Jesus as what? The savior. But
few people understand him as what? The
king. Right? We talk about heaven,
blessings, eternal life, right? But we
don't consider what it truly means to
live what? Under authority.
to live under authority because not
everyone
knows what order looks like,
right?
Some people just make up in their mind
they going to buck the system, right?
Some people enjoy going against the
grain, right? Everybody doesn't like
order, right? But we know with the Lord,
everything is done what? Dec order,
right?
So, what does it truly mean to live
under authority?
Here's a question I want to ask.
Are we living as children of the kingdom
that we expect to inherit?
that we expect to inherit? See, because
you can't wait till you're in the
kingdom of God
to start acting what? godly.
>> Amen.
>> Right. This is something that we have to
start doing right now.
>> Right now.
>> Right. Because we're actually
auditioning right now. The movie will be
played back whether you make it in the
kingdom of God.
>> Right. Well, you going to be in the
kingdom of God. It's just what side you
going to be on.
>> Right. So, as we celebrate Pentecost
weekend,
we're reminded that God did not just
send his Holy Spirit just to give us an
experience. He sent his spirit to
prepare us, to inspire us, to equip us
for a ruler that would reign as king.
So, with that in mind, I entitled a
lesson today, thy kingdom come.
preparing for preparing for the rule and
reign of Christ. And as always, I like
to give you an overview of preparing a
lesson like this. What what were my
objectives that I want to deliver?
First, we'll take a look at the kingdom
and its king. You know, what is the
kingdom? Who is the king and why it
matters? We'll kind of take we'll
transition. We'll look at the kingdom
and its citizenship. the environment of
the kingdom and it and becoming citizens
of it. And last but not least, we'll
kind of transition. We'll take a look at
thy kingdom come and preparing for that
kingdom. You know, the millennial reign,
the restoration, and making ourselves
ready. Y'all ready?
>> Amen. Let's get him.
>> Let's get it.
>> So, let's first establish Jesus as king.
Because once again, we know him as a
savior, but not many people know him as
king. Let's go to Matthew the 2 chapter.
Matthew the 2 chapter.
So, everyone says Jesus is my personal
savior.
You know, and some of those oneliners I
wish was 100% true. I know we all do,
right? Jesus is my personal savior.
Sounds great,
but the word of God tell us that
salvation is common.
>> You know, you got to put forth your hand
to the plow, not only and grab on to it,
but hold on to it. That's
>> right.
I tell you, that's why Philippians 3:13
has become one of my new found
scriptures that I love. You know,
Paul said this one thing I do,
forgetting those things which are behind
and reaching forth those things of which
are before me, right? We all got a past,
but Paul saying, you know what? I'm
looking forward. Can't change none of
that.
>> Right. But what I can do is repent and
do good works indeed and be judged on
those things.
>> Right.
>> That's right.
>> Matthew the 2 chapter, let's dive right
in. Pick it up at verse one, brother. Go
ahead. Now when Jesus was born in
Bethlehem of Judea in the days of Herod
the king, behold, there came wise men
from the east to Jerusalem.
>> Mean S, you must have one of those new
Bibles, right? I know it say three wise
men from the east.
>> It says, "Behold, there came wise men
from the east to Jerusalem."
>> Not three, not 3,000.
>> Gave no number.
>> Gave no number. Right? So these wise men
came uh to the east to Jerusalem saying
what?
>> Saying where is he that is born king of
the Jews? For we have seen his star in
the east and are come to worship him.
>> So now they looking for
this person that was going to be born
right king of the Jews. This was not
something that uh the people were going
to select.
He was born to be king of the Jews.
Right? Let's go to John the 18th
chapter.
See, because Pontious Pilot is going to
ask Jesus a question that we're going to
pay close attention to the answer to
because
all throughout the scripture, we we read
where Herod, he would go to the elders
and seek these answers because guess
what? They had the oracles of God. They
had the answers
and everybody knew where to go to get
the answers.
Say, "Where is he that is born king of
the Jews? Say, we've seen his star in
the east and are come to worship him."
John 18.
This is during the trial of Jesus
and Pontus Pilot is going to uh ask
Jesus a very important question. John 18
pick it up at verse 33 brother and you
can go ahead and start to read. Then
Pilate entered into judgment into the
judgment hall again.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And called Jesus and said unto him, "Art
thou king of the Jews?"
>> So he punches finally come into the
judgment hall again. right? Cuz he
trying to work this thing out. He didn't
want to go forward with this. The
people, the elders were were the people
were pressing uh uh Pontious Pilot to to
continue with this trial. Excuse me. I'm
slow down. Right.
Saying unto him, "Art thou the king of
the Jews?" Go ahead. Jesus answered him,
saying, "Thou this thing thou sayest
thou this thing of thyself? or others
tell it tell it thee of me?
>> Uh-huh.
>> Pilate answered, Am I a Jew? Thine own
nation and the chief priests have
delivered thee unto me, what hast thou
done? So listen, Pilate say, listen, am
I a Jew? He said, your own people
delivered you up to me. That's right.
Right. He say, what did you do?
What did you do to get these people this
mad that they want you dead?
Crucify him. Crucify him. Right. They
say, "Let his blood be on us and our
children."
Right? Bunch of power like, "What did
you do to these people?" Continue to
read
>> 36. Jesus answered, "My kingdom is not
of this world. If my kingdom were were
of this world, then would my servants
fight?"
>> So, wait a minute. We need to establish
something right out the gate. See,
because there are people who say, "We in
the kingdom right now."
>> Y'all heard it too, huh?
>> Right. Jesus say, "My kingdom is not of
this world." Right?
>> If my kingdom were of this world, then
my servants would fight. Continue to
read. That I should not be delivered to
to the Jews.
>> But now is my kingdom not from hence.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Pilate therefore said unto him, "Art
thou a king?" Then Jesus answered, "Thou
sayest that I am a king. To this end was
I born, and for this cause came I into
the world, that I should bear witness
unto the truth. Everyone that is of the
truth heareth my voice." So Pontious
Pilot say, "You know what
you say?" Oh, he said, "Are you the king
of the Jews?" Right? He says, "Are thou
a king?" Then Jesus said, "Thou says
that I'm a king." Right? He said, "But
you know what? I'm going answer you with
this." Right? To this end was I born.
For this cause did I come into the
world. I didn't come into the world just
to be a savior. But I also came to be a
king. But not at my first coming. Right?
Not at his first coming did he come to
be king. Because see, here's the thing.
If you're a king, you got to have a
kingdom.
>> That's right.
>> Right. With that said, let's go to
Revelation the third chapter.
Because see, this is what goes over the
world. They don't understand that when
you start speaking of the kingdom of
God, right? You have to be very
definitive because there are two.
There's the kingdom of the son, there's
the kingdom of the father.
>> That's right.
>> Right.
And I remember sometimes uh sometime
last year a brother called me and uh we
were trying to get uh a brother to see
this and
you know that little idol in his mind
just wouldn't let him see it.
We tried though but the Lord say you got
an ear to hear let him hear. You can't
make a person hear. You can't make make
a person understand. Only God can open
up your understanding.
>> That's right.
>> And he chooses when to do it.
>> Amen.
>> Revelation three, pick it up at verse
20, brother, and go ahead and read.
Behold, I stand at the door and knock.
If any man hear my voice and open the
door, I will come into him and will s
with him and he with me. So listen, did
the Lord say, I stand at the door and
knock? Is the Lord talking about one of
those physical doors?
Y'all sure? Y'all say everybody come.
But the Lord said, "No, I come to the
door and knock." He's talking about of
your mind.
>> The door of your mind. That's right.
>> Right. The Lord say, "I'll have someone
expose the word to you. I'll deliver my
word to you. And if you receive it, if
you'll open up your mind to receive it,
he say, you know what? I'll come in and
I'll sit with you.
>> All right? I'll give you some
understanding. Continue to read
>> 21. To him that overcomemeth will I
grant to sit with me in my throne.
>> Wait a minute. But the Lord say even
after that if you open up your mind to
grab this understanding. He say if you
are overcome overcome what? Overcome
yourself.
>> See like I said the most important
person you going to talk to every day is
who?
>> Yes sir.
>> The person you looking in the mirror.
>> That's right.
>> The Lord say if you will overcome not
only yourself but the world. He he say I
will grant uh you to sit with me in
what?
>> In my throne.
>> My throne.
>> I never promise you the father's throne.
>> Continue to read.
>> Even as I also overcame and am sat down
with my father in his throne.
>> Now, how can the average person not see
that there's two different thrones
there?
>> Right? But if you have that little idol
in your head, you can't see it. Right?
But he's saying, "I will grant uh uh for
you to sit with me in my throne, even as
I overcame and sit down with my father
what?" In his his throne. Two totally
different thrones. He never promised us
the father's throne. He promised us to
sit down with his throne. If we overcome
though,
>> that's right.
>> Right. Because see, part of that
overcoming is denying yourself. Right.
Because this flesh wants it all. This
flesh wants what it want. Right? Even
the things that it know it shouldn't
have, it has desires. But let's look at
Jesus at his first coming. I said once
again, uh, that he didn't come to
establish his kingdom, but he did come
to save man. Let's go to Luke the first
chapter
because some will say we're in the
kingdom now, which is scary because if
this is the kingdom,
>> you got hunger,
right? You got people being taken
advantage of. You got crime at record
rate. If this is the kingdom,
>> sin is rampant,
>> right? There are some islands that you
know as a snapshot would seem better
than anything we read about as far as
what God say his kingdom is.
>> God say all that offend won't be in his
kingdom
not where he is.
See, but I think the problem is, you
know, the Lord sometimes all throughout
the scripture, he gives us physical
things, of course, to show us spiritual
things.
So,
people re get wrapped up in their mind.
They get caught up on even the spiritual
aspect of being kingdom minded
and forget that the Lord speaks of a
physical kingdom that's to come. But
we're going to establish that before
this lesson's over. I promise you. Luke
1, pick it up at verse 30, brethren, and
you can go ahead and start to read.
>> And the angel said unto her, "Fear not,
Mary, for thou hast found favor with
God."
>> So wait a minute. The angel come up on
Mary,
>> right? He first thing he told her, "Fear
not." Reading and reasoning, clearly he
saw she was afraid. But every time you
talk to somebody, the when the Holy
Spirit came up on them, right?
No fear.
>> Every time you read in the scripture
where somebody was being entertained or
be or entertaining an angel, right,
there was some kind of fear that was
involved.
>> Cuz you at that time, you dealing with a
spirit being with power.
>> Power.
>> Why wouldn't you be afraid?
>> That's right.
>> First, you want to make sure you're
dealing with what? A Holy Spirit.
You know, that's why it's it it's you
have to be extremely careful when people
say, you know, I go to speaking in in
tongues and I'm in the spirit,
>> right? How do you know who you
entertaining at that point?
>> If Satan know that, you know what, I can
get you to that level. You're so all
caught up and that's when I'll deal with
you.
I know you got to be careful, right? But
I don't challenge anybody because that's
your experience. I know as for me, no, I
just wait to hear his voice through this
word. That's enough for me. I don't need
to be entertained by nothing other than
that. Right.
>> Amen.
>> Pick it up at verse 31, though, brother.
Let's go.
>> And behold, thou shalt conceive in thy
womb, and bring forth a son, and shall
call his name Jesus.
>> So, wait a minute. Mary didn't even she
didn't even name her own child.
>> No. No, she did not.
>> The name came from on high.
>> From heaven. That's right. The father
say told told the uh angel you go tell
Mary the child that should be born his
name going to be Jesus. Continue to
read.
>> He shall be great
>> and shall be called the son of the
highest.
>> And the Lord God shall give unto unto
him the throne of his father David.
>> So stop it. Has the throne of his of
David ever been in heaven?
>> No.
>> Right. The throne of David has always
been established on earth in Jerusalem.
Right. But the scripture say that he
shall be great. He shall be called the
son of the highest and the Lord God
shall give him unto him uh the throne of
his father David. Go ahead.
>> And he shall reign over the house of
Jacob forever
>> which is Israel. Go ahead.
>> And of his kingdom there shall be no
end.
>> And of his kingdom.
>> His kingdom.
>> Possessive pronoun. Right. We all took a
little English in school, right? This
kingdom it say there shall be no end
because see this kingdom is none other
than the first resurrection.
>> When this kingdom comes it it it it
introduces the millennium. The it comes
at the seventh trump.
>> It's the first day
of what we consider the rest time.
Right? The when when Satan will be bound
for a thousand years, there will be
peace on earth. is all pointing toward
this time. Let's go to Isaiah the 9th
chapter. But because see all of this was
prophesied.
All of this was prophesied.
See, this is how
when we get to the New Testament, this
is how all the apostles knew what they
were looking for.
That's why they would ask Jesus, "Have
you come to restore the kingdom?"
Because they knew that not only was he
coming as a savior, but he also was
coming as king of the Jews.
Isaiah 9.
And I want us to play catch because this
is this is the end of the gentile
dynasty here.
You know, and the scripture going to
tell us that this government
will be established in the kingdom of
God.
Isaiah 9,
pick it up at verse six, brother, and
you can go ahead and start to read.
>> For unto us a child is born.
>> Uhhuh. Unto us a son is given.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And the government shall be upon his
shoulders.
>> And this government is nothing other
than rulership.
>> Telling us that a child was going going
to be born. A son was going to be given.
And the government shall be upon his
shoulder. Go ahead. And his name shall
be called wonderful counselor, the
mighty God, the everlasting father, the
prince of peace.
>> Why the prince of peace?
Come on, Bible scholar. Somebody talk to
me today. I mean, come on. Because there
will be peace on earth at this time,
right? When this kingdom is set up,
there will be peace on earth. Because
remember, Satan's going to be bound for
what?
>> Thousand years.
>> So, the peace breaker will be bound. So,
the Lord will be prince of peace,
>> wonderful counselor, the mighty God, the
everlasting father.
>> I've said it all the time. See Jesus
carry
all the titles that the father carried
>> right? It's just the father don't carry
some of the titles that Jesus carried,
right? But so when you start talking
about the everlasting father, talking
about Jesus right here. Start talking
about the mighty God, talking about
Jesus right here. Glory to God. The most
high in Deuteronomy the 25th chapter. We
talking about Jesus right there. Right.
Continue to read at verse 7 though,
brother.
>> Of the increase of his government and
peace there shall be no end. Uhhuh. upon
the throne of David and upon his kingdom
to order it and to establish it with
judgment and with justice from
henceforth even forever. The zeal of the
Lord of hosts will perform this.
>> Say the zeal of the host, right? L the
Lord of hosts will perform this, right?
It says upon the throne of David and
upon his kingdom, right? to order it and
to establish it with judgment and
justice from henceforth even forever.
Even in the Old Testament, it was being
established that you know what, there
would be a earthly kingdom. Right? Let's
go to Daniel's the seventh chapter.
Daniel 7. But it told us that the zeal
of the Lord of hosts would perform this.
That the government would stand upon his
shoulders
and of the increase of his government
there shall no end.
>> Peace and there shall be no end.
It's going to be an exciting time.
>> A time like we've never known.
>> We've never known true peace. Right.
There's never been uh a part of man
history where there has just been total
peace.
>> That's right. That's right.
>> Daniel 7.
See, but just as God
will be in this kingdom of God, he also
give us an opportunity
as saints to be in this kingdom of God.
Because here in Daniel the 7th chapter,
this is the end of the gentile rule. And
we're going to I want to establish that
the saints will possess the kingdom and
this kingdom will be none other than on
earth. Let's go to Daniel 7.
Pick it up at verse 13, brother.
>> And you can go ahead and start to read.
>> I saw in the night visions, and behold,
one like the son of man came with the
clouds of heaven.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And came to the ancient of days, and
they brought him near before him.
>> That's right. And this is the father
speaking to the son. Go ahead.
>> And there was given him dominion.
>> There was given him a dominion. Go
ahead.
>> And glory and kingdom. and that all
people, nations, and languages should
serve him. His dominion is an
everlasting dominion which shall not
pass away, and his kingdom that which
shall not be destroyed.
>> Right. Cuz there will during the time of
Jesus kingdom, Jesus rule, there will be
only one government in place.
>> That's right.
>> Right. Skip down to verse 21.
Go ahead. I beheld, and the same horn
made war with the saints.
>> Uhhuh. And prevailed against them until
the ancient of days came, and judgment
was given to the saints of the most
high. And the time came that the saints
possessed the kingdom. Wait a minute. So
the saints, they didn't stand in
judgment, right? It say judgment was
given to the saints. So I'm going ask by
your hand, right? You rather stand in
judgment or you or you rather be one
judging.
>> Rather be one judge. One judge because
you you doing the judging. You in a good
fight.
>> That's right.
>> He say the saints shall possess the
kingdom. Right. The kingdom will be
given in the hands of the saints. And
who are the saints?
>> Those that keep the testimony and the
faith of Jesus Christ.
>> That's right. Revelation 14 and 12 say,
"Here are the patience of the saints.
Here are they that keep the commandments
of God." And what? and the faith in
Jesus. You got to have both.
>> Gotta have both.
>> You gotta have both, right? So, if you
plan to be a uh considered as a saint,
you got to keep them commandments, but
you got to have faith in Jesus also.
Skip down to verse 27, brother, and go
ahead and read.
>> And the kingdom and dominion, and the
greatness of the kingdom under the whole
heaven,
>> above under the whole heavens.
>> So, if it's under the heavens, where is
it?
>> On the earth. On the earth. But y'all
some well taught people.
>> Praise God.
>> It says, "And the kingdom and dominion
and the greatness of the kingdom under
the whole heaven, go ahead. Shall be
given to the people of the saints of the
most high."
>> That's right.
>> Whose kingdom is an everlasting kingdom.
And all dominion shall serve and obey
him. That's right. And our hope once
again is to be in that number.
>> Amen.
>> Of one of the saints
>> ruling and reigning with Christ.
>> Right. Let's go to uh Psalms 132nd
chapter. Psalms 132.
See, because not only is the Lord giving
us an opportunity to be saints, but the
Lord speaks of training up a child in
the way
because behavior is taught.
The Lord saying, "I just lent you these
children." He says, "All souls are
mine."
>> All souls.
>> Psalms 132.
Psalms 132.
Pick it up at verse 11, brother. I don't
hear any more pages.
Go ahead.
>> The Lord has sworn in truth unto David.
Say the Lord has sworn in truth unto
David. Go ahead.
>> He will not turn from it.
>> No, sir.
>> Of the fruit of of the fruit of thy body
will I sit upon thy throne.
>> Uhhuh.
>> If thy children will keep my covenant
and my testimony that I shall teach
them, their children shall also sit upon
thy throne forever more. So listen at
that. So the Lord is saying not only
you, he said, but if you will teach your
children, right, I'll give them an
opportunity
>> to sit upon thrones. Which throne is he
speaking of?
>> Jesus's kingdom, right? How do I know
that? Continue to read, brother. For the
Lord has chosen Zion.
>> And another name for Zion is just
Jerusalem. Go ahead. Heath desired it
for his habitation. This is my rest
forever. Here will I dwell for I have
desired it.
>> So the Lord say I have chosen Zion.
>> Right? And once again like say uh
another name for uh Zion is just
Jerusalem. He say for I have desired it
for his habitation. Just somewhere you
where you dwell.
>> He said this is my rest forever. Here
will I dwell for I have desired it.
Right? But now Jerusalem would just
serve as the headquarters because the
Lord tell us that the entire earth is
mine and the fullness thereof. Right? He
say though we would just come up to
Jerusalem to keep the feast of
tabernacle. Right?
Jerusalem would just serve as the
headquarters. He says this is my rest
forever. Here will I dwell. He say for I
have desired it. Right? Let's go to Luke
the 22nd chapter
because this is Jesus speaking with the
disciples.
Those who have continued with him in his
temptation
concerning the kingdom of God. See,
because God know that this walk isn't
easy. That's why he says to him that
>> overcome
>> that overcome will I grant to sit with
me what?
>> In my throne. and my throne.
So just as he was speaking to the
disciples, he's speaking to us
because you do have to overcome a lot.
Mainly that person that we look at in
the mirror each and every day.
>> That's the biggest obstacle every day.
Luke the 22nd chapter.
When you get there, brother, you can
pick it up at verse 28.
Ye are they which have continued with me
in my temptation. So the Lord is
speaking to the to the the apostles at
this time because they went through a
lot,
you know, because you you have to
seriously look at the day in the life of
the apostles even when they was with
Jesus, right? They were always being
confronted by the the uh the scribes and
the Pharisees. They're always being
tested, right? A lot of times we read
they were always in one.
Continue to read. and I appoint unto you
a kingdom as my father hath appointed
unto me. So, but the Lord is saying, you
know what, if you if you overcome,
right? He say, I'll appoint unto you a
kingdom as my father has appointed unto
me. Continue to read,
>> that ye may eat and drink at my table in
my kingdom, and sit on thrones, judging
the 12 tribes of Israel.
>> But the Lord say, you know what? If you
overcome, I'll allow you to sit in my
kingdom. and sit on throne judging what
the 12 tribes of Israel.
>> So you won't be in judgment. You'll be a
part of the ruling and reigning uh
saints that are doing the judging.
>> That's right.
>> Right. But let's take a look here. Let's
go to Revelation the second chapter.
Revelation the second chapter
because I know before I came into the
truth
when I would think of uh
now we refer to it as the kingdom of
God. But you know, you think about being
in heaven, you thought about, you know,
I guess all the cartoons we seen, you
know, just flying around with wings on,
you know,
but let's be honest, after about two
days of that, you'd be like, what's
next?
You know,
I walked in the ways of the Lord for 50
years. I just get wings to fly around.
No, no.
But the Lord said, "You know what? Eyes
have not seen, ears have not heard."
>> That's right.
>> Right. What I have in store for those
that love me. Cuz I mean, once again,
this small man, I can think of some
great things
just here on earth, you know, that I
could f, you know, I could feel 24 hours
of just enjoyment.
But the Lord say, "Ears have not heard,
eyes have not seen."
Man, y'all know y'all like to go see
what's going on on Jupiter. What y'all
doing over here?
Don't nobody else mind think like that?
Okay. All right. All right. All right.
All right. All right. All right. All
right.
Pray for me cuz my mind do go there.
But what is it that God promised the
saints? Go to Revelation the 2 chapter.
Pick it up at verse 26, brother. And go
ahead and start to read. And he that
overcomemeth and keepeth my words, my
works unto the end. Man, the Lord always
box us in,
>> right? See, the Lord saying you can't
just say, "Hey, Lord, I I serve you
early 2000s."
>> Can I get some credit?
>> Uhoh. What have you done for me lately?
Man, the Lord always boxes. He said,
"You got to do this to you got to do
these works until the end." Continue to
read. To him will I give power over the
nations, and he shall rule them with a
rod of iron. As the vessels of a potter
shall they be broken to shivers, even as
I received of my father. That's right.
So the Lord, he is giving us an
opportunity to rule and reign with him.
Right. He said, you gonna have power
over the nations.
That's why he say those that will will
will be faithful over little man just
think the Lord you've done the will of
the Lord. He say you know what I want
you to be over five nations
right
you be over two you can't handle that
but it says you shall rule them with a
rod of iron and see the Lord because
once again he's still about order. There
will still be uh children born during
this time. There still will be time for
correction. But the Lord's giving you an
opportunity to rule and reign with him.
Let's look at this same message but in a
parable. Let's go to Luke the 19th
chapter.
Let's look at the same message that we
just read in Revelation the 2 chapter.
But the Lord is going to give it to the
apostles in a parable.
Like I said, the Lord would always give
us something in the physical to show us
something in the spiritual.
That's the only way we could comprehend
it. That's just like now.
You know, there are just things that we
can't explain even though we see it in
the physical.
But one day we will.
Luke 19,
let's pick it up at verse 11, brother.
And you can go ahead and start to read.
>> And as they heard these things,
>> he added and spake spake a parable.
>> Speak this parable. Go ahead, brother.
>> Because he was nigh to Jerusalem and
because they thought that the kingdom of
God should immediately appear. So once
again, even during that time, they
didn't think that they were in the
kingdom of God, right? But they did
think since, you know what, since the
savior is here, since the one that was
born to be king, since he's here,
maybe the kingdom starts now,
right? They even had that thought in
that back and in that day. But the
Lord's going to lay on on them this
parable. Go ahead, brother, and start to
read. He said, "Therefore, a certain
noble went into a far country to receive
for himself a kingdom and to return."
>> So you know the Lord is talking about
himself, right? So this nobleman is none
other than the Lord in this far country
is heaven.
>> He said he went to receive it for
himself a kingdom. But here's the most
important thing to return. To return,
>> right? Because there will be a second
coming.
>> Continue to read though, brother. What's
going on in this parable? And he called
his 10 servants and delivered them 10
pounds and said unto them, "Occupy till
I come."
>> But his citizens hated him and sent a
message after him, saying, "Will we not
have this man to reign over us?"
>> They saying that now,
you know, we don't have to do those
commandments. God placed that on the
Jews.
>> That's not for us in this day and time.
What makes us so different?
Are we righteous where we don't need
logs?
>> Makes no sense. Continue to read though,
brother. And it came to pass Uhhuh.
>> that when he had he was returned, having
received the kingdom, then he commanded
these servants to be called unto him to
whom he had given the money that he
might know how much every man had gained
by trading.
>> Oh, so the Lord want to know what it is
that you did with what I entrusted you
with. M
>> right.
>> That's right.
>> Cuz see the Lord gives gifts and talents
but sometime we we we we take like the
scripture say we take too much upon
ourselves. We think
it's for us. We think it's for the
world. Right? The Lord is saying what
did you do with what I gave you?
I know he won't ask me that by no voice
though.
Hey. Hey. kill them.
Be like, "Lord, you know you ain't give
me no vote."
But back to the story at 16, brother.
Then came the first saying, "Lord, thy
pound hath gained 10 pounds."
>> So Lord, with what you entrusted me
with, I went and did the will of the
Lord, and I brought in 10 pound. I
brought I brought in increase.
>> I labored in your vineyard. Amen.
>> Continue to read, brother.
>> And he said unto him, "Well, thou good
servant, because thou hast been faithful
in a very little, have thou authority
over 10 cities."
>> So listen at that, since you went out
and did and labored in the vineyard,
right? You went out and increased in the
earth
when we ruling and reigning. Right? You
were faithful were little. I'm going
place you over 10 cities
to rule and reign. Continue to read. And
the second came, saying, Lord, thy pound
hath gained five pounds. And he said
likewise to him, be thou also over five
cities. So likewise, you went out and
did what you needed to do. There is
increase. Right? This represents the
ruling and reigning with the Lord. This
is what he promises us. Right? Let's go
to Revelation the 20th chapter.
Revelation the 20th chapter.
>> Amen.
>> Revelation 20.
>> See, cuz once again, this is the
millennial reign. We're going to see
that ruling and reigning with Christ was
always one of the many blessings that
the Lord was giving us an opportunity to
take part in. That's why he say to him
to overcome
>> will allow to sit with me on my throne
ruling and reigning.
>> Amen.
>> That's just one aspect. We're going to
look at more.
Revelation 20.
Pick it up at verse one, brother, and
you can go ahead and start to read.
>> And I saw an angel come down from
heaven.
>> So, was that angels with an S or that's
just one?
>> That's just one.
>> That's just that's just plural, right? I
mean, that's just singular. Singular.
So, one angel came down from heaven. Go
ahead.
>> Having the key of the bottomless pit and
a great chain in his hand.
>> Uh-huh. What did he do? and he laid hold
on the on the dragon that old serpent
which is the devil and Satan and bound
him a thousand years. So once again, big
bad Satan, the devil. The Lord say he
only sent one angel,
>> one
>> to bound him.
>> Just one.
>> That's all he need.
Bound him for a thousand years. Now we
can have peace on earth. Continue to
read. And cast him into the bottomless
pit and shut him up and set a seal upon
him that he should deceive the nations
no more till the thousand years should
be fulfilled. And after that, he must be
filled. Excuse me. And after that, he
must be loosed a little season.
>> Because guess what? See, God is a is a
even-handed God. He's fair. How fair
would it be for them to live a thousand
years
>> with no tempter there, with no accuser
there,
>> right? No, the Lord, he going to loose
him for a season,
>> right? But here it is. You've been
living, ruling. Well, because once
again, that will be flesh
>> and blood. That's right. and and
immortal in the kingdom of God.
>> So those that those fleshly beings that
had never been tempted by Satan,
wow, what a blessing.
>> But the Lord say, I'm only going to
bound him, but then he's going to be
loose for a season. He going to get a
chance to try them also cuz fair is
fair. Continue to read.
>> And I saw thrones and they that sat upon
them and judgment was given unto them.
>> So does that throne have an S?
So he say I saw a throne because the
Lord has given us an opportunity as
saints to sit on those thrones. Remember
continue to read. And I saw the souls of
them that were beheaded for the witness
of Jesus and for the word of God and
which had not worshiped the beast
neither his image, neither had received
his mark upon their foreheads or in
their hands. And they lived and reigned
with Christ a thousand years.
>> So let's just clear our mind for just a
second. We keep reading that, right? But
I really want you to think about, take
that in. You ruling and reigning with
Christ.
>> He making calls. You making calls.
Ruling and reigning with Christ.
>> I know where my mind just went. I pray
y'alls went there, too. Continue to
read. But the rest of the dead live not
again until the thousand years were
finished. This is the first
resurrection. Blessed and holy is he
that take part that has part in the
first resurrection. On such the second
death hath no power, but they shall be
priests of God and of Christ and shall
reign with him a thousand years.
>> That's right. Let's go right on over to
Revelation the 5th chapter because we
see we're reigning and ruling with
Christ for a thousand years.
Put emphasis on this. Where is it?
>> Right here on the earth.
Pick it up at verse 9, brother.
Revelation 5. Pick it up at verse 9.
And they sung a new song, saying, Thou
art worthy to take the book, and to open
the seals thereof.
>> Uhhuh. But thou was slain, and has
redeemed us to God by thy by thy blood
out of every kindred and tongue and
people and nation, and has made us unto
our God kings and priests. And we shall
reign on the earth.
>> Reign where?
>> Reign on the earth. Reign on the earth.
This is where the ball park will be
played. God
>> at in this ballpark on the earth. Right.
Let's go to Philippians the third
chapter.
But because see I want to show you at
you know during this time the saints
will be given a glorified body.
You know that's that's the one thing the
church would always say you know hey
they waiting on their glorified body.
They got that right
because it's scriptural.
The Lord promised the saints a glorified
body at the first resurrection at the
millennium at his kingdom.
during the time of peace.
Philippians the 3 chapter,
pick it up at verse 20, brother.
Go ahead.
>> For our conversation is in heaven.
>> Our conversation is in heaven. Go ahead.
>> From whence also we look for the Savior,
the Lord Jesus Christ.
>> That's right. We looking for that
savior. Go ahead. Who shall change our
vile body that it may be fashioned like
unto his glorious body according to the
working whereby he is able even to
subdue all things unto himself.
>> That's right. to the Lord say he going
to change our vow body into what
glorious bodies that's what we looking
forward to see but these are some of the
questions they had even when he was on
the earth let's go to Luke the 20th
chapter we knew that a change has to
happen
and the Lord is going to give us a
marvelous illustration here in in Luke
the 20th chapter
see because the saints that make the
first resurrection. They going to have
that glorified body.
>> Luke 20,
pick it up at verse 27, brother. When
you get that, you can go ahead and start
to read.
Then came to him certain of of the
Sadducees which denied that there is any
resurrection and they asked him
>> so wait a minute first of all they don't
even believe there's a resurrection
right but then they want to ask him
questions about the resurrection
continue to read saying master wrote
unto us if any man's brother die having
a wife and he die without children that
his brother should take his wife and
raise up seed unto his brother
>> man I'm glad this lost don't still
stand today.
>> That's right.
That was too much, y'all.
>> That's the truth.
>> All right.
The one for the day. All right.
>> 29.
>> Hey, now. Hold on. We can't go. We got
to break that one down.
>> Okay. If a man brother die having a
wife, right, and brought up no seed to
him because once again the land was
everything, right? So if you had a son,
it could be your your inheritance stayed
in the family if you had a son, right?
Or a seed. Continue to read.
There were therefore excuse me.
>> Mhm.
>> 29.
>> 29. There were therefore seven brethren,
and the first took a wife, and died
without children, and the second took
her, took her to wife, and he died
childless. And the third took her, and
in like manner the seven also, and they
left no children, and died. Can you
imagine?
You done went through your whole family
>> being like the fifth of six.
>> You like
it just ain't happening.
>> We're down to the seventh brother.
>> There's still no seed, right?
>> But they going the SE, they're going to
ask a fair question. Go ahead. Continue
to read
>> 32. Last of all, the woman died also.
>> Uhhuh. Okay. The woman died also. Go
ahead.
>> Therefore, in the resurrection, whose
wife of them is she?
>> For seven had her to wife.
>> You know, even though they poking the
bear, that's a legitimate question,
right?
>> But you know, the Lord is going to have
an answer for them. Continue to read.
And Jesus answering said unto them, "The
children of this world marry, and are
given in marriage, but they which shall
they which shall be accounted worthy to
obtain that world and the resurrection
from the dead, neither marry nor are
given in marriage."
>> So the Lord saying once again, cuz you
going to have that glorified body if you
come up in the resurrection. The Lord
talking about those things you talking
about, that's that's fleshly. That's
earthly.
>> That's earthly. He ain't going to be
concerned about that,
>> right? That's what the Lord is trying to
teach him. Continue to read. Neither can
they die anymore. That's the most
important thing.
>> Amen.
>> Neither can they die anymore. Go ahead,
brother. For they are equal unto the
angels and are the children of God.
>> Being the children of the resurrection,
>> being children of the resurrection. So
if you one of those saints, you one of
those children of the resurrection, you
going to die no more,
>> right? You going to be equal with the
angels. That's why the Lord had to come
up with something for the angels cuz the
angels once again they're spirit beings.
They don't die.
>> So the Lord, he came up with something
though. He got that lake of fire, right?
>> He did.
>> So when the Lord returned, there will
still be flesh and blood peep up on the
earth. But once again, we'll still be
marrying and and and and there will
still be marrying and dying in the
kingdom of the son. Let's continue to
read. Let's go to uh let's go to Isaiah
the 65th chapter.
Once again, just taking a look at some
of the life in the kingdom of the sun.
He said you're going to be the prince of
peace
cuz they say we're in the kingdom now
and
we in the kingdom now, but we got
violence everywhere. You know, the first
10 minutes of the news, you're like,
"Oo, ah, oo."
You know, this is the kingdom, man. This
is scary.
But the Lord, just a little glimpse of
the the kingdom that he speaks of is
something to be rejoicing in and it's
something to be desired.
Isaiah 65,
pick it up at verse 19, brother. And
when you get there, you can go ahead and
start to read.
>> And I will rejoice in Jerusalem.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And joy in my people, and the voice of
weeping shall be no more heard in her.
>> Uh-huh. When is this? Continue to read.
>> Nor the voice of crying. There shall be
no more thence an infant of days, nor an
old man that had not filled his days.
For the child shall die in 100 years
old, but the sinner being 100 years old
shall be in a curse. Can you imagine
that?
Somebody died at a 100 years old. You
like, man, what did they do?
>> What did they do that they died at a
100? That's going to be strange.
Continue to read. And they shall build
houses and inhabit them. And they shall
plant vineyards and eat the fruit of
them.
>> Uhhuh.
>> They shall not build and and excuse me
and another inhabit. They shall not
plant and another eat. For as the days
of a tree are the days of my people.
Think about that.
>> The Lord is saying as the lifespan of a
tree, that's going to be the reflection
of my people.
You got some of those big redwoods in
California.
>> Hundreds.
>> I mean, these things tall as buildings.
They so tall. They they they so large
and so old. They they they cut out the
middle and they drive cars through them.
But they still standing.
The Lord is saying, "During my time,
this would be a representation of my
people." Continue to read.
>> And mine elect shall long enjoy the work
of their hands.
>> Uhhuh. They shall not labor in vain, nor
bring forth for trouble, for they are
the seed of the blessed of the Lord, and
their offspring with them. And it shall
come to pass that before they call, I
will answer. And while they are yet
speaking, I will hear.
>> So yeah,
>> the Lord say before you even call,
right? He said, I will answer.
>> Right. He's with you the entire time.
Yes.
>> See, while you yet speaking, I will
hear. Continue to read. The wolf and the
lamb shall feed together, and the lion
shall eat straw like the bullock, and
dust shall be the serpent's meat. They
shall not hurt nor destroy in all my
holy mountain.
>> So the Lord sayith the Lord.
>> So the Lord has given us, he's saying
this is going to be the time of peace,
right? He's saying the wolf and the
lamb, they going to feed together.
Praise God. So, if we're in the kingdom
of God like they say we are, like Pastor
Buy say, we should be able to do the
test, right?
>> Put a wolf and a lamb together, watch
them feed together. That's not the case.
>> Ain't going to happen.
>> That ain't going to happen.
>> Say the lion shall eat straw like the
bullock.
>> It's not the case. Right. Let's go to
Zechariah the 8th chapter.
She doing the kingdom of the son. There
will be total peace
because the peace breaker will be bound
and the king of kings
and lord of lord he will be reigning.
Zechariah the 8th chapter.
Hold on.
Zechariah 8.
Zechariah 8. Pick it up at verse one.
When you get there, brother, you can go
ahead and start to read.
>> Again, the word of the Lord of hosts
came to me, saying,
>> What did he say? Thus sayeth the Lord of
hosts, I was jealous for Zion with great
jealousy, and I was jealous for her with
great fury.
>> So the Lord loves that area. Right? He
said, I was jealous for Zion. Continue
to read.
>> Thus great jealousy. Go ahead.
>> Thus sayeth the Lord,
>> I am returned unto Zion, and I will
dwell in the midst of Jerusalem, and
Jerusalem shall be called a city of
truth.
>> Is Jerusalem called the city of truth
right now?
>> No. We know this is future, right? There
is no larger gay parade to date
>> than what they hold in Jerusalem every
year. That is terrible. Terrible.
>> Just think about nowhere on the planet.
Google it when you get a chance. Don't
do it now. Largest gay parade in the
world.
It's definitely not called a city of
truth right now.
>> Right. Pick that up at three again,
brother. Go ahead.
>> Thus sayeth the Lord, I am returned unto
Zion. The Lord say when he returned to
Jerusalem, go ahead. Zion,
>> and will dwell in the midst of
Jerusalem,
>> and Jerusalem shall be called a city of
truth, and the mountain of the Lord of
hosts, the holy mountain.
>> Mhm.
>> Thus sayeth the Lord of hosts, there
shall yet old men and old women dwell in
the streets of Jerusalem, and every man
with his staff in his hand for a very
age, and the streets of the city shall
be full of boys and girls playing in the
streets thereof. Imagine that for a
second. When the last time you seen uh
boys and girls just playing in the
street in peace?
>> Ain't even coming outside anymore.
>> They got them PlayStation 8s.
>> Yeah,
>> I know. I I
Yeah, they got them PlayStation 8s. They
ain't going outside.
But it says the old men and the old
women shall dwell in the streets of
Jerusalem.
Right. Continue
to read.
>> Six. Thus sayith the Lord of hosts.
>> Uhhuh.
>> If it be marvelous in the eyes of the
remnant of his people in these days
should it also be marvelous in mine
eyes.
>> And see and and that's where I was
trying to go with it. Right. It's a
beautiful sight when we see you know
kids playing enjoying themselves. The
Lord said if it be pleasant in your
sight, how do you think I feel when I
see it? M
>> a creation that I created functioning
how I designed it.
>> Continue to read though, brother. Sayeth
the Lord of hosts, thus sayeth the Lord
of hosts, behold, I will save my people
from the east country and from the west
country, and I will bring them, and they
shall dwell in the midst of Jerusalem,
and they shall be my people, and I will
be their God in truth and in
righteousness. and in truth and in
righteousness. So no matter what goes on
of dispute come up, just know it's going
to be dealt with in truth and
righteousness.
>> Everybody going to get what they deserve
when they deserve it.
>> That's right.
>> Skip down to verse 20.
Thus sayeth the Lord of hosts,
>> Uhhuh.
>> It shall yet come to pass that there
shall come people and the inhabitants of
many cities, and the inhabitants of one
city shall go to another.
>> And what are they going to be saying,
brother? Go ahead. saying, "Let us go
speedily to pray before the Lord and to
seek the Lord of hosts. I will go also."
>> So, are they saying that now?
>> No.
>> They say, "Let us go speedily to pray
before the Lord and to seek the Lord of
hosts, right?" Just imagine you got you
got something that's really on your
mind.
>> You ain't got to go to no deacon, no no
assistant. You can go to the Lord
>> himself and get a pure answer. He say
what? In righteousness and truth.
>> Continue to read though, brother.
>> Yeah. Many people and strong nations
shall come to seek the Lord of hosts in
Jerusalem and to pray before the Lord.
>> What a wonderful sight. Continue to
read, brother. Thus sayeth the Lord of
hosts, in those days it shall come to
pass that 10 men shall take hold out of
all languages of the nations, even shall
take hold of the skirt of him that is a
Jew, saying, we will go up with you, for
we have heard that God is with you. Now,
I know this happened to somebody here
last week. Somebody grab Somebody grab
your shirt or your skirt and say, "Hey,
listen. We want to go with you because
we know that the Lord is with you.
>> We're in the kingdom.
>> I know that didn't happen.
>> No.
>> What happened to you last week?
>> Not that.
>> Give a testimony.
>> Get Get a go get a Lord some credit
right now.
>> This hadn't happened.
>> This has not happened.
>> Say 10 million shall grab hold out of
all languages.
Right.
Take hold of the skirt of him that is a
Jew saying we will go with you
>> for we have heard that God is with you.
That in itself going to be a marvelous
sight,
>> right?
>> You know because that's why God truly
created us. He said what? You were going
to be a king and a priest, right? You
were going to go forth and what? Show
forth my glory. That was the job from
the very beginning to go and grab all
the other nations and bring them unto
God.
But we went and we learned of their
ways.
>> Right. Let's go to Zechariah the 14th
chapter.
Zechariah 14.
Because I want to show you even when the
Lord returned with the saints, we still
going to be keeping some of the feasts.
Can you imagine that? I mean, we looking
forward to tomorrow. Can you imagine
going keep the feast with the Lord
himself there?
>> Man, I see I see some smiles in the
crowd. They're like, "Yes."
>> Amen. Amen.
>> What What they say? What they say? What
they say uh at the wedding he waited
till the last to bring out the good
grape the good wine.
>> Good wine
>> man
like what's this?
>> Well that's that's some that's some
heavenly grapes. All right. All right.
All right. Zechariah 14. Y'all be going
there.
>> But man keeping the feast with the Lord
himself there.
>> himself.
I I guarantee we bring up our best then.
>> I guarantee you we bring up our best.
>> Be at home.
>> Oh yeah. This is it. I'm presenting
this. Zechariah 14. Pick it up at verse
three, brother. Go ahead. Then shall the
Lord go forth and fight against those
nations as when he fought in the day of
battle. And his feet shall stand in that
day upon the Mount of Olives, which is
before Jerusalem on the east. And and
the Mount of Olives shall cleave in the
midst thereof, toward the east, and
toward the west. And there shall be a
very great valley, and half of the
mountain shall remove toward the north,
and half of it toward the south.
>> And he shall flee to the valley of the
mountains, for the valley of the
mountain shall reach unto Azol. Yeah, ye
shall flee like as ye fled from before
the earthquake in the days of Uzziah,
king of Judah, and the Lord my God shall
come and all the saints with thee. So
imagine that cuz when the Lord first
return, of course, he's going to take
take it by force, right?
>> So imagine you coming back and you
fighting with the Lord. You're talking
about not taking the L.
I mean, you can go get your big brother,
your your uncle who ain't never you
showing back up with the Lord. The Lord
coming back with all the saints.
>> I already feel sorry for the other team,
right? Skip down to verse nine.
And the Lord shall be king over all the
earth. That's why I said earlier once
again, Jerusalem would just serve as the
headquarter, right? The Lord said he
going to be king over all the earth at
this time. Continue to read.
>> In that day shall there be one Lord and
his name one. That's right. So we ain't
going to be arguing over no name, no J,
no something somebody read off the
internet that didn't exist 5 years ago.
We won't be doing any of that. Right?
Skip down to verse 16 though, brother.
This is why we come here. And it shall
come to pass that everyone that is left
of all the nations, which came against
Jerusalem, shall even go up from year to
year to worship the King, the Lord of
Hosts, and to keep the feast of
tabernacles.
>> He said, "You still going to be keeping
the feast of tabernacles."
>> That's right.
>> But then you know some people, they
going to say, "I ain't going up." Go
ahead. 17. And it shall come and it
shall be that whosoever will not come up
of all the families of the earth unto
Jerusalem to worship the king the Lord
of hosts even upon them shall be no
rain. So I guarantee you they come the
following year when them crops don't
come in. When the Lord don't let it rain
on your crops I guarantee you going
I guarantee
>> the Lord say you know what you don't
want to come up.
>> Okay. He say
>> you ain't going to get no rain.
>> You know drought and famine going to sit
in then.
>> I guarantee I see you the following year
>> if you can make it through the year.
>> Right.
>> Continue to read though, brother.
>> 18.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And if the family of Egypt go not up and
come not that have no
>> that have no rain, there shall be the
plague where we the Lord will smite the
heathen that come not up to keep the
feast of the tabernacles. Uh-huh.
>> This shall be the punishment of Egypt,
and the punishment of all nations that
come not up to keep the feast of
tabernacles.
>> That's right. Cuz the Lord know his
creation. Let's go to Isaiah the second
chapter.
>> The Lord said, "Y'all don't want to come
up and keep a feast with me, you won't
get no rain.
>> No rain, no food, no
>> just a matter of time.
Isaiah the second chapter.
See, because here the Lord is going to
enlighten us that once again it's going
to be total peace on earth. Men will
learn war no more. No more. It will
start off with a little war, but the
Lord is quickly going to end that and
then we will have peace on earth. Only
at that time, Isaiah the 2 chapter, pick
it up at verse one, brother, and you can
go ahead and start to read.
>> The word that Isaiah, the son of Amos,
saw concerning Judah and Jerusalem.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And it shall come to pass in the last
days,
>> so we talking about this will happen in
the last days. Continue to read that the
mountain of the Lord's house shall be
established in the top of the mountains
and shall be exalted above the hills and
all nations shall flow unto it. And many
people shall go and say, "Come ye, and
let us go up to the mountain of the
Lord, to the house of the God of Jacob,
and he will teach us of his ways, and we
will walk in his paths. For out of Zion
shall go forth the law, and the word of
the Lord from Jerusalem,
>> and he shall judge among the nations,
and shall rebuke many people.
>> But not only will he be judging the
nations, also will the saints will be
there, too. But continue to read.
>> And they shall bear, and they shall beat
their swords into plowshares, and their
spears into pruning hooks. Nation shall
not lift up sword against nation,
neither shall they learn war anymore.
>> That's right. That's what life will be
like in the kingdom of the son.
>> Amen.
>> War no more. Right. Let's go to Luke the
13th chapter.
Right.
>> War no more. We can't even imagine a
world without war.
You know
men will go to war over anything now.
minerals.
>> Definitely power
>> sometimes just to flex. You go destroy a
country like like what was that for?
What did you go conquer the land? Did
you want the land? Did you enslave the
people? No. We just we just bonded for
10 years and came home.
We didn't want the all. We didn't take
the all. We just bonded them for 10
years.
Luke 13
cuz like I say the Lord give us little
small samples. I want to show you, you
know, some of who will be in this
kingdom.
We could have went to Hebrews 11th
chapter, but we're going to read from
Luke the 13th chapter today. Just a just
a few. Luke 13, pick it up at verse 22,
brother. And you can go ahead and read.
>> And he went through the cities within
villages, teaching and journeying toward
Jerusalem.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Then said one unto him, Lord, are there
few that be saved?
>> And he said unto them, Strive to enter
into the straight gate, for many, I say
unto you, will seek to enter in and
shall not be able. Mhm. When when once
the master of the house is risen up and
has shut the door and ye begin to stand
without and to knock at the door,
saying, Lord, Lord, open unto us, and he
shall answer, and say unto you, I know
you not so which ye are.
>> Like Pastor Buie say, he ain't talking
to street people right here. Right.
These are those, as the scripture would
say, who who who knew his will and did
it not.
>> Did it not,
>> right? These these are people who claim
to be believers.
Continue to read 26. Then shall ye begin
to say, "We have eaten and drunken in in
thy presence." Uh-huh. And thou hast
taught in our streets.
>> But he shall say, I tell you, I know I
know you not, which ye are. Depart from
me, all ye workers of iniquity.
>> Oh my gosh. Go ahead.
>> There shall be weeping and nashing of
teeth. when you shall see Abraham and
Isaac and Jacob and all the prophets in
the kingdom of God
>> of some of the prophets
>> all the prophets.
>> So the Lord say Abraham, Isaac, Jacob
and all the prophets going to be in the
kingdom of God.
>> So the question is
are what we doing? Are we doing the
things that are necessary to where we
can be in there?
>> We read about all the other people. Are
we securing our place to be in the
kingdom of God? Right? Because you won't
just, you know, uh, find yourself in
there and you're not doing the things of
God. That's not going to happen. Not on
the right side of it anyway. Pick it
back up at 28 from the top. There shall
be weeping and nashing of teeth.
>> Uhhuh. when ye shall see Abraham and
Isaac and Jacob and all the prophets in
the kingdom of God, and you and you
yourselves thrust out,
>> and they shall come from the east and
from the west and from the north and
from the south, and shall sit down in
the kingdom of God.
>> That's right. So once again we just as
we saw earlier you know some of the the
um apostles and the prophets uh I want
to show you that we also can be included
into that number. Let's go to Matthew
the 19th chapter once again.
Matthew 19
because it's important to
know that once again it's obtainable.
All we got to do is go get it.
>> That's right.
Because Peter's going to ask the Lord a
very direct and important question. One
in which sometimes we
may ask ourselves because this walk it
gets hard. Right? Anybody say
this walk is easy, you fooling yourself
or you're not and you're not doing it
right because this is a hard walk,
right? Because you got to deny yourself.
You got to put God first in all
situations and just human nature. We
don't want to do that.
Matthew 19, pick it up at verse 27,
brother, and go ahead and start to read.
Then answered Peter and said unto him,
"Behold, we have forsaken all and follow
thee. What shall we have therefore?"
>> That's a that's a legitimate question,
isn't it? You know, because the Lord
says uh uh he is a reward of them that
diligently seek him.
You know, he say if you overcome
uh for those that have overcome with me
in my temptation. Peter saying we
forsaken all and follow thee. You know
what should we have therefore?
Legitimate question. Go ahead, brother.
What did he tell him? And Jesus said
unto them, "Verily, I say unto you, that
ye which have followed me, in the
regeneration, when the Son of man shall
sit on the in the throne of his glory,
ye also shall sit upon 12 thrones,
judging the 12 tribes of Israel."
>> Man, and and you know that that's a
great answer. That's a great answer. You
know, because in my small little mind,
you know, judging the 12 tribes of
Israel, that seemed like work to me. But
but I have I have to retrain this
thought in you once again. You're in the
kingdom of God. So don't worry about
that.
>> Right? But the most important thing is
what we'll read next. Go ahead, brother.
And everyone that hath forsaken houses
or brethren or sisters or father or
mother or wife or children or lands for
my name's sake shall receive a hundfold
and shall inherit everlasting life. So
once again the Lord is saying everyone
has forsaken house brethren sister
father wife children land for my sake
>> he said you shall receive a hund 100fold
he's talking about even in this life
right because I know we we share our
testimonies amongst each other a lot of
times and we say you know what when I
come into this truth man my mother
forsake me my father don't speak to me
anymore right My my siblings, they don't
want to have anything to do with me.
Right. But I ask you,
yeah, if your mother forsake you, how
many mothers do we have in here?
>> Come on now.
>> Right. How many brothers do you have in
here?
>> Amen.
>> How many sisters do you have in here?
The Lord say, I'll give you a hundfold.
He's talking about even right now.
>> Amen.
>> Because this is where we come and we
draw strength,
>> right? Because it do get tough. But the
most important thing that we will read
in 29 is the very end. He say shall
inherit eternal life. Right? Eternal
life is the biggest gift that we can
receive from God
to live forever. Right? Let's go to
Ezekiel the 37th chapter.
Because during this time,
this is when the Lord say he's going to
put the two sticks back together.
We know that the nation had been split
that Judah and Israel, the Lord split
the tribes up never to be, you know, uh
the lost tribe. That's why they
considered the lost tribe. Never to be
joined back together again. But here in
Ezekiel the 37th chapter, this is when
the Lord is saying that you know what?
I'm going to make those two sticks one.
I'm going to put the nation back
together during this time.
Ezekiel the 37th chapter,
pick it up at verse 19, brethren, and
you can start to read. Say unto them,
thus sayeth the Lord God,
>> behold, I will take the stick of Joseph,
which is in the hand of Ephraim, and the
tribes of Israel, his fellows, and will
put them with him, even with the stick
of Judah, and make them one stick.
>> So the Lord is saying, at that time, I'm
going to make them one stick. When is he
going to do this? Continue to read,
brother. And they shall be one in mine
hand.
>> And the sticks whereon thou whereest
shall be in thine hand before thine eye
before their eyes. And say unto them,
thus sayeth the Lord God, behold, I will
take the children of Israel from among
the heathen, whether they be gone, and
whether and will gather them on every
side, and bring them into their own
land.
>> So once again, we know that the lost
tribe, they still lost, right?
We know that they still off. We know
that, you know, Judah, you know, they
got a chance to go back and and and and
and start to rebuild the temple, but for
the most part, all of Israel was once
they were scattered, they never came
back, right? As the nation of Israel,
but listen to here at 22. Go ahead,
brother. And I will make them one
nation.
>> The Lord say, "But at this time, I'm
going to make them one nation." Go
ahead, brother.
>> In the land upon the mountains of
Israel.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And one king shall be king to them all.
Yes, sir.
>> And they shall be no more two nations,
neither shall they be divided into two
kingdoms anymore at all.
>> So the Lord said this one, I'm going to
put the nation back together. You're
going to be able to look and see uh uh
uh Asher and G all of all the tribes
will be there under one king.
>> We know that this has to be during the
kingdom. Continue to read though,
brother. Neither shall they defile
themselves anymore with their idols, nor
with their detestable things, nor with
any of their transgressions. But I will
save them out of all their dwellings,
>> out of all their dwelling places,
wherein they have sinned, and will
cleanse them. So shall they be my
people, and I will be their God.
>> And this is what's going to help stamp
it at 24. Go ahead, brother.
>> And David, my servant, shall be king
over them.
>> Wait a minute. David been Acts the
second chapter tell us David is dead and
Bar and his supplicant is with us until
this day.
>> Right? So the Lord say when he put them
two nations together back together he
say
>> David going to be king over them.
>> How? Because David going to come up in
that first resurrection. That's right.
>> Continue to read though, brother.
>> And they all shall have one shepherd.
>> Who who you think that shepherd's going
to be?
>> Jesus.
>> That's right, brother. Continue to y'all
some well taught people. Go ahead. They
shall al also walk in my judgments and
observe my statutes and do them.
>> We know we talking future. Go ahead,
brother. And they shall dwell in the
land that I have given unto Jacob my
servant wherein your fathers my have
dwelt. And they have dwelt well therein.
Excuse me. And and they shall dwell
therein and even they and their children
and their children's children forever.
and my servant David shall be their
prince forever.
>> Continue to read.
>> Moreover, I will be a covenant of peace
with them. Excuse me. I will make a
covenant of peace with them. It shall be
an everlasting covenant with them, and I
will place them and multiply them, and I
will set my sanctuary in the midst of
them forever more.
>> My tabernacle also shall be with them.
Yeah. I will be their God and they shall
be my people. So the Lord is saying
during this time I'm going to be their
God. They going to be my people in the
kingdom of the son. Right? Let's go to
first Corinthians the 15th chapter
because we established earlier that once
again there are two kingdoms, two
thrones. But I want to show you when
Jesus will turn his kingdom over to the
father.
1 Corinthians the 15th chapter.
It's why Jesus put a time stamp on here.
It's called the thousand-year reign.
>> That's right.
>> The millennial
because after this point, Jesus will
turn his kingdom over to the father.
1 Corinthians 15, pick it up at verse
20, brother. Once you get there, you can
go ahead and start to read. But now is
Christ risen from the dead, and become
the first fruits of them that slept.
>> That's right. Go ahead.
>> For since by man came death, by man came
also the resurrection of the dead.
>> Uh-huh.
>> For as in Adam all die, even so in
Christ shall all be made alive.
>> But every man in his own order, Christ
the first fruits, afterward they that
are Christ at his coming. And see, and
this is how we know for certain that
there's nobody already have received the
promise that are that's in heaven.
Because the the Lord say he got to be
the first fruits.
>> He's the first to die and go back
>> to sit on the right hand of the father.
Right? He says, "But after this,
afterward they that are Christ at his
coming, this is when you receive your
reward for being a a great servant." But
continue then at 24, brother.
>> The end cometh the end. Uh-huh.
>> When he shall have delivered up the
kingdom to God, even the Father, when he
shall have put down all rule and all
authority and power, for he must reign
till he has put all enemies under his
feet. The last enemy that shall be
destroyed is death. He said the last
enemy that's going to be destroyed is
death. He said, but he going to deliver
up the kingdom of God to the father. Let
me show you that. This is when thy
kingdom should come of the father. Our
last scripture, Revelation the 21st
chapter.
Revelation 21.
Jesus going to deliver up his kingdom to
the father because once again he has
already reigned king of king and lord of
lords.
Now, it's time for the father to usher
down
the kingdom of the father, which is
still the kingdom of God.
Because God is a spirit, and they that
worship him must worship him in spirit
and in truth.
>> That's right.
Revelation 21,
pick it up at verse one, brother, and
you can go ahead and start to read. And
I saw a new heaven and a new earth, for
the first heaven and the first earth
were passed away, and there was no more
sea.
>> And I, John, saw the holy city, New
Jerusalem, coming down from God out of
heaven,
>> prepared as a bride adorned for her
husband. So just imagine this for a
second. New Jerusalem, it's already
completed,
>> right? The father and the son looking at
it right now. It's done. It was finished
from the foundation of the world.
It's weighed on us.
Continue to read. Three. And I heard a
great voice out of heaven, saying,
Behold, the tabernacle of God is with
men, and he will dwell with them, and
they shall be his people, and God
himself shall be with them, and be their
God.
>> My God. Go ahead, brother. And God shall
wipe away all tears from their eyes. And
there shall be no more death, neither
sorrow nor crying, neither shall there
be any more pain. For the former things
are passed away. And he shall and he
that sat upon the throne said, "Behold,
I make all things new." And he said unto
me, "Write, for these words are true and
faithful." That's right. Because once
again, once this kingdom, there will be
no more death, no more sorrow, no more
crying. Because remember, in the kingdom
of the son, a sinner was going to die at
what?
>> 100 years old.
>> Some people are listening today at 100
years old. But now that we're in the
father's kingdom, there will be no more
death, no more sorrow, no more crying,
neither shall there be any more pain.
Right? The former things are passed
away. God will be draining
will be dwelling in the midst of his
people. Once again, I pray that you got
some understanding of the kingdom of God
to come.
Amen. Amen.
Oo
hey.